它们这么做 是出于自身原因吗
Like, is it for them?
不 我觉得是为我们着想
No, we think it's for us.
内厅的空气似乎不与外界流通
The air doesn't seem to circulate inside the chamber,
所以你们进去两小时后 就会感觉缺氧
so after about two hours, you run out of oxygen.
只不过是通风换气
It doesn't take 18 hours
不需要每次都等十八小时吧
to pump fresh air into a room.
大气成分
Atmosphere.
什么
Excuse me?
如果它们的大气成分与地球不同
If their atmosphere is different from Earth,
那么每次打开门前
it would certainly take hours
就真的需要十数小时
to rebalance the O2 content and pressure for us
来平衡压强与氧气含量
every time they open their door.
你是说 它们随时能让我们窒息而死吗
So, you're saying they could suffocate us if they wanted?
这是中央情报局的大卫·哈尔彭探员
This is Agent David Halpern with the CIA.